Come back in this section we're going to look at the Project Management components the different parts
of a project.
So the things that we didn't know as a project manager in as a PMP candidate in this lecture we're going
to look at the different components of project management and how they work together very important
that we don't need to just have these silos of project management but it's integrated that they work
together.
So that's one of the things we'll discuss is the project management process groups and the project management
knowledge areas.
Recall your PMP Exam has those five exam domains and those are based on the process groups across the
process groups we have knowledge areas and those are the different chapters in the Timba.
So our process groups initiating planning executing monitor controlling and closing are integrated or
crossed with the different knowledge areas chapter for the Pinback through 13 trade integration management
scopes schedule cost quality resources communication risk procurement and stakeholders.
They kick out a lot but those are the knowledge areas so process groups and knowledge areas go together.
And so we have a really important assignment where you're going to map out those processes.
So you're going to have exposure to the entire Pinback in detail in this section.
So if you've been hungry to get into some deeper material or some more exams specific material now is
your opportunity.
A lot of things to talk about and cover.
We're also going to look at a Pinback concept of tailoring the processes something that you do in any
organization.
Adaptive environments.
So this is new to him Box 6 if you're working in a scrum or add Jayal or XP or lean programming those
are adaptive.
We'll talk about adaptive environments and we're going to look at the project business case and a benefits
management plan two really important concepts for your exam so you can see this is a really big section
with a really big assignment that I want you to complete.
So we'll talk about that as we get to that point of course.
Let's get going.
I'll see you in the next lecture.